export default [
  {
    key: "0",
    title: "JavaScript",
    creationDate: Date.now(),
    cards: [
      { front: "What´s the best way to create a matrix?", answer: "Array.from(Array(6), () => Array(3))", type: "Remember card", key: "0", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "How to get the values of an object", answer: "Object.values(obj)", type: "Fill card", key: "1", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "How to get the largest value of an array?", answer: "Math.max(...arr)", type: "Fill card", key: "2", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "When I use a method like call to change the context, what happen if I pass null or undefined as the context", answer: "It will take the global object as the context", type: "Remember card", key: "3", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
    ],
  },
  {
    key: "1",
    title: "Spanish",
    creationDate: Date.now(),
    cards: [
      { front: "Amend", answer: "Enmendar", type: "Fill card", key: "0", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "Hi, how are you?", answer: "Hola, cómo estás?", type: "Fill card", key: "1", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "Food", answer: "Comida", type: "Fill card", key: "2", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "Airport", answer: "Aeropuerto", type: "Fill card", key: "3", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "Hi, my name is", answer: "Hola, mi nombre es", type: "Fill card", key: "4", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "How was your day?", answer: "Cómo estuvo tu día?", type: "Fill card", key: "5", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "I have two brothers and two sisters", answer: "Tengo dos hermanos y dos hermanas", type: "Fill card", key: "6", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
    ],
  },
  {
    key: "2",
    title: "Company business contract",
    creationDate: Date.now(),
    cards: [
      { front: "Payment", answer: "Provider will invoice Client for Services performed within 7 days of performance. Client will pay Provider as set forth in each Statement of Work within 5 days of receipt and acceptance of such invoice. It is understood that payments to Provider for services rendered shall be made in full as agreed, without any deductions for taxes of any kind whatsoever, in conformity with Provider’s status as an independent contractor.", type: "Remember card", key: "0", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "Limitation of liability", answer: "In no event will either party be liable for any SPECIAL, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES.", type: "Remember card", key: "1", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
    ],
  },
  {
    key: "3",
    title: "Business laws and regulations",
    creationDate: Date.now(),
    cards: [
      { front: "Law 1 - Tax Code", answer: "Every company registered within the United States has to pay federal taxes. Most companies will also have to pay state taxes, depending on the state in which the company is registered. These are unavoidable. Avoiding taxes—or deciding not to pay them outright—comes with hefty penalties and potential jail time.", type: "Remember card", key: "0", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "Law 2 - Employment and Labor Law", answer: "Equal opportunity: Most employers with at least 15 employees must comply with equal opportunity laws enforced by the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission (EEOC). The EEOC mandates that certain hiring practices, such as gender, race, religion, age, disability, and other elements are not allowed to influence hiring practices.", type: "Remember card", key: "1", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "Law 3 - Antitrust Laws", answer: "Any time a company conspires with its competitors, third-party vendors, or other relevant parties, it may run afoul of antitrust laws.", type: "Remember card", key: "2", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "Law 4 - Advertising", answer: "A good advertising strategy can do wonders for your business. But before you dive in, you’ll need to make sure that you’re playing by the rules and government regulations. For example, you have to make sure the claims in your ads are not untruthful or purposely deceptive. Using testimonials in your ads comes with additional regulations. Violating these rules can result in fines, which defeats the purpose of your advertising in the first place.", type: "Remember card", key: "3", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "Law 5 - Email Marketing", answer: "Closely related to advertising is email marketing. If your business engages in email marketing, there are separate regulations you’ll need to comply with under the CAN-SPAM Act.", type: "Remember card", key: "4", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now() },
      { front: "What should you do if your client broke the law?", answer: "Meet with him immediately to see what the consequences are", multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: ['Accuse him', 'Congratulate him', 'Wait and see what happens'], type: "Multiple choice card", key: "5", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now() },
    ],
  },
  {
    key: "4",
    title: "Lawyers",
    creationDate: Date.now(),
    cards: [
      { front: "What should you do if your client broke the law?", answer: "Meet with him immediately to see what the consequences are", multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: ['Accuse him', 'Congratulate him', 'Wait and see what happens'], type: "Multiple choice card", key: "5", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now() },
    ],
  },
  {
    key: "5",
    title: "React",
    creationDate: Date.now(),
    cards: [
      { front: "What are hooks?", answer: "Hooks are functions that allows us to work with the state in functional components.", type: "Remember card", key: "0", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "How to declare a state variable using hooks?", answer: "const [myVar, setMyVay] = useState('initialValue)", type: "Fill card", key: "1", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
    ],
  },
  {
    key: "6",
    title: "Português",
    creationDate: Date.now(),
    cards: [
      { front: "Hi my name is", answer: "Oi meu nome é", type: "Fill card", key: "0", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "where is the airport", answer: "onde é o aeroporto", type: "Fill card", key: "1", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
      { front: "I need to go to my hotel", answer: "Preciso ir ao meu hotel", type: "Fill card", key: "2", lastReview: Date.now(), nextReview: Date.now(), multipleChoiceIncorrectAnswers: [null, null, null] },
    ],
  },
]